Hilda Mason, City Council 029
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1
  - Police Surveillance Hobson 1 of 2, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Police Surveillance Hobson 2 of 2, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Bill 1-287 Non- Criminal Police Surveillance Act 1 of 2, 1975-1977 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Bill 1-287 Non- Criminal Police Surveillance Act 2 of 2, 1975-1977 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Population Projects, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Thomas J. Porter, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Bill 3-316 Prayer, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Presidential Bldg. Rent, 1980-1983 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Procurement 1 of 2, 1985-1989 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Procurement 2 of 2, 1985-1989 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Public Emergency of Disaster, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Public Works CTEE Rules, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Committee of the whole Dennis Desmond, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Recorder of Deeds Nomination, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Rent Eviction Delaeffe v Riley, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Rented Bldg.'s - DC Gvt. Etc., 1980-1981 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Board of Education Schools Closed etc., 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Leasing to Sale of Public Lands, 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Initiative #17 (overnight shelter), 1982-1984 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Agenda Minutes 1 of 3, 1941-1983 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Agenda Minutes 2 of 3, 1941-1983 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Agenda Minutes 3 of 3, 1941-1983 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Education and libraries April 30 1990 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Memos, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Voting Rights Fundraiser Event 1 of 2, 1983-1986 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Voting Rights Fundraiser Event 2 of 2, 1983-1986 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Real Property Leases Randall to Grimke Buildings, 1983-1994 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - DC Public Schools 1 of 2, 1981-1988 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - DC Public Schools 2 of 2, 1981-1988 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Rental Housing Cost Hearings Nov. 1978 1 of 2 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Rental Housing Cost Hearings Nov. 1978 2 of 2 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Reprogrammings 1 of 4, 1981-1985 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Reprogrammings 2 of 4, 1981-1985 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Reprogrammings 3 of 4, 1981-1985 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Reprogrammings 4 of 4, 1981-1985 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Reprogramming Policy and Funds Control Act 1 of 3, 1979-1987 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Reprogramming Policy and Funds Control Act 2 of 3, 1979-1987 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Reprogramming Policy and Funds Control Act 3 of 3, 1979-1987 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Ellington School, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Residency General 1 of 3, 1972-1984 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Residency General 2 of 3, 1972-1984 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Residency General 3 of 3, 1972-1984 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Residence - Hicklin V Orbeck (Alaska), 1978 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Revenue Anticipation Notes, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Revenue (Tax) Legislation Filed 2/3/84, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Reid Inez Smith, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Riggs Bank, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Rules and Regulations Municipal Regulations, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Sex Discrimination, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Sexual Assault, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - U.D.C Original Act 1974 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - UDC Alumni Trustees, 1952-1983 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - UDC Trustees Compensation, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - U.D.C Miner Bldg., 1976 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - U.D.C "The Dinner Party", 1974 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - UDC Procurement Regulations, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - U.D.C Appointment of Trustees Amend. Act 1989 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - UDC Budget Clarification, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - U.C.D Farrrakhan, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - UDC Map, undated (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - U.D.C Presidents Contract, 1985-1988 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - U.D.C Presidents Dic Fund, 1981-1985 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - U.D.C Middle States Assn., 1985 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - University of D.C. Mount Vernon Campus 1 of 2, 1974-1990 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - University of D.C. Mount Vernon Campus 2 of 2, 1974-1990 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - U.D.C S Clark, 1984-1985 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - University of D.C Trustees Meeting Material, 1981-1989 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - UDC Trustees BD Meetings, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - UDC Trustees BD Meetings, 1983-1984 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - UDC Board of Trustees Legislation Committee Reports, 1974-1983 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - U.D.C Labor Negotiations, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - UDC Management Plan, 1986-1987 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Education Pay Raises U.D.C Dept. Chairs, 1984-1987 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Education Pay Raises U.D.C Dept. Chairs, 1984-1987 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - U.D.C R.I.F, 1985-1987 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - U.D.C - Street Academy, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - U.D.C Student Membership Profile, 1983-1984 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - U.D.C Trustees- List of Names/wards/Addresses etc., 1983-1986 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - UDC Trustees- Desirable Qualifications, undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Education and Libraries Regular Meeting 9/20/93, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Site Value Taxation, 1934-1980 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Sludge, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Doris T. Smith (Pay/leave/etc.), 1982-1986 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Smoking, 1986-1988 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Sovereign Immunity, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Special Education, 1980-1987 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - State of the District - 1983 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Statehood Constitution - 1987 AMDT (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Sunshine Law, 1975-1990 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Street Lighting 1 of 2, 1984-1985 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Statehood Constitution Convention, undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Street Lighting 2 of 2, 1983-1984 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Surveyor Fees - 1979 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Swimming Pools, 1983-1984 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Takoma Traffic Pattern, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Tax-Exempt Properties (All Soul's etc.), 1985 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Tax Statistics, 1977-1990 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Kyra Tirana, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Traffic Problems, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts Driver Education Rent Payments, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Unemployment Compensation, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Unitarian Universalist Assn., 1984 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - UDC Trustees - 1983 Nominations 1 of 3, 1983-1989 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - UDC Trustees - 1983 Nominations 2 of 3, 1983-1989 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - UDC Trustees - 1983 Nominations 3 of 3, 1983-1989 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - UDC Trustee - 1982 Vincent Reed Berry (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - UDC Trustees - 1979 Nominations (Barry) (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - UDC - 1984 Trustee Nominations (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - UDC Trustees - 1978 Nominations (W. Washington) (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - UDC Trustee Nomination RJ Reynolds Adopted (6 December, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - UDC Trustee Nominations Original Group Res. Adopted 20 April 1976 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - UDC Trustees- Expiration Date of Terms Issue, 1982-1983 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - UDC Tuition, 1980-1985 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Education - UDC Tuition, 1982-1983 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - UDC Trustees - 1993 Confirmations (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Education and Libraries Special Meeting, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - U.D.C Tuition Grants for AFDC Parents, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Exhibit G to civilization No. 5418-82, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Report of the Search Committee for the Presidency of UDC, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - University of D.C - Wilmer, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - University of D.C, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - UDC Defendants Pleadings, 1977-1982 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Education Public hearing on UDC Trustee Nominees, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - UDC 1 of 5, 1984-1985 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - UDC 2 of 5, 1984-1985 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - UDC 3 of 5, 1984-1985 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - UDC 4 of 5, 1984-1985 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - UDC 5 of 5, 1984-1985 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - University of District Columbia Non Appropriated Budget FY 1985, 1984-1985 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Education- Public Hearing September 19 1985 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Education- Public Hearing September 19 1985 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Education - Public Hearing September 23 1985 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - March 17 1980., 1985 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Education-Public Hearing Monday September 9 1985 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Education/Recreation/Youth Affairs 1 of 2, 1976-1980 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Education/Recreation/Youth Affairs 1 of 2, 1976-1980 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Veterans Preference, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Video Arcade Legislation, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - An Wang, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Bruce I. Waxman, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Workers Compensation GW Central Labor Council v D.C., 1980-1982 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Youth Pride Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Zoning Materials 1 of 4, 1970-1986 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Zoning Materials 1 of 4, 1970-1986 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Materials 1 of 4, 1970-1986 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Materials 1 of 4, 1970-1986 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - UDC FY 1990 Supplemental Request (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Upshur St. Clinic Spivey v Barry, 1980-1981 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - UDC Office of Development in Testimony Charges, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - DC Office of Personnel 1 of 2, 1983-1985 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - DC Office of Personnel 2 of 2, 1983-1985 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Charly/Hilda Mason, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - The President and University of the District of Columbia, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Letters to judges and supplemental letters, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Curriculum Design Review Conference, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - DC Law 11-52 Merger Agreement/Budget Chronology/Transcript/UDC Letter, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - The Miner Building: A Historical Landmark, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - May 19- RE: DCSL Lease, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - A Bill in the Council of the District of Columbia, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - 1988 Legislation Correspondence (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Correspondence, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Report on the Committee on Education, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - 1988 Reprogramming (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Feb. 22 1988 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - FY 1955 Budget Correspondence and Newspaper Clippings, 1990-1995 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1994-1995 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Law School 1 of 6, 1989-1996 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Law School 2 of 6, 1989-1996 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Law School 3 of 6, 1989-1996 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Law School 4 of 6, 1989-1996 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Law School 5 of 6, 1989-1996 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Law School 6 of 6, 1989-1996 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - DC Law School Robinson Correspondence, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Resignation of Dean Jones, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Public School of Law Amendment Act of 1989 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Education and libraries Oct. 16 1989 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - FY 1989-1990 Budget Memos and Correspondence (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Interim Board of Governors 1 of 2, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Interim Board of Governors 1 of 2, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - DC Law School Orientation Package, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - IGB Correspondence - Agendas and Amendments 1 of 4, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - IGB Correspondence - Agendas and Amendments 2 of 4, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - IGB Correspondence - Agendas and Amendments 3 of 4, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - IGB Correspondence - Agendas and Amendments 4 of 4, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Educational and Career Services Policies and DC Law School Application Catalog, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - UDC Law School and Antioch Law School 1 of 7, 1986-1987 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - UDC Law School and Antioch Law School 2 of 7, 1986-1987 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - UDC Law School and Antioch Law School 3 of 7, 1986-1987 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - UDC Law School and Antioch Law School 4 of 7, 1986-1987 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - UDC Law School and Antioch Law School 5 of 7, 1986-1987 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - UDC Law School and Antioch Law School 6 of 7, 1986-1987 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - UDC Law School and Antioch Law School 7 of 7, 1986-1987 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Antioch Law School, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Antioch University, 1874 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Antioch- Dymally Hearing Material, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Prevocational School Site, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - District of Columbia Public Library 1 of 2, 1988-1990 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - District of Columbia Public Library 1 of 2, 1988-1990 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - DC School of Law Correspondence and Reports, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - DC Law School Legislation, 1989-1990 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Board of Governors Correspondence and Agendas, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Public School of Law Acts and Bills, 1989-1990 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Honorable Hilda H.M Mason, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Law School Amendment Act 1989, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Law School Amendment Act 1989, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Law School Accreditation and New Building Pre-Voc Site, 1989-1990 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Proposed Development of the Prevocational School Site, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - The Development of the Prevocational School Site, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - The Development of the Prevocational School Site, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Hazel v. Barry, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Development Proposal of the Prevocational School Site, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Proposed Development for the Educational Facility for DC Law School 1 of 2, undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Proposed Development for the Educational Facility for DC Law School 2 of 2, undated (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - 1992-93 Litigation Docket, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Re Charter Amendment Regulation, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Bd. Ed. Long range plan, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Cleveland School, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Capital Pulpit - 1994-1996 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday May 1 1989 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Additional Meeting Friday April 11, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries April 24 1989 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday September 26 1988 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday January 23 1989 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday January 9 1989 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries FY: 90 Budget Hearing 2/13/89, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Agency Hiring of Private Attorneys, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Review of Contract between DC Board of Ed and Willie L. Leftwich of D.C Relating to Asbestos Removal in D.C Public Schools, undated (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Roundtable Discussion Council Member Mason April 20 1988 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday 10/22/90, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries 6/13/1988 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries June 30 1989 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries May 8 1989 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Meeting Monday April 11 1987 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday June 11 1990 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday June 4 1990 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Public Hearing Tues 2/13/90, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Employment, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Ketchum Case, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Additional Meeting Feb. 9 1990 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday Dec. 11 1989 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Public Hearing 12/18/89, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Frank Smith, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Everson Electric, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Budget Hearing February 17 1989 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries FY 90 Budget Markup March 10 1989 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday March 13 1989 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Regular Meeting Monday April 10 1989 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday October 23 1989 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday Nov. 13 1989 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday June 8 1989 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday April 27 1987 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday July 10 1989 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Public Hearing Tues. 2/13/90, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday Jan. 22 1990 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Public Hearing Council Member Mason March 23 1989 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday February 25 1988 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday Feb. 27 1988 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday Nov. 23 1987 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Charles N. Mason Hilda Mason's Office District Building - Room 122, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Additional Meeting October 14 1988 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Congressional Records, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Report to Congress of the D.C Governments Residency Requirement for New Hires Pursuant to House of Rep. Report 99.675, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Public Hearing FY 1989 Internal Budget, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Report to Congress of the D.C Governments Residency Requirement for New Hires Pursuant to House of Rep. Report 99.675, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Congressional Record, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Proposed Career and Excepted Service Salary and Pay Increase FY 1987 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Managing the Nation's Capital, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Toward Recovery, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees of the University of the District of Columbia Confirmation Resolutions, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Ed. And Libraries Additional Meeting 3/31/94, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Education and Libraries Regular Meeting 6/21/93, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Education and Libraries Regular Meeting 7/06/93, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Education and Libraries Regular Meeting 6/28/93, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Education and Libraries Regular Meeting 6/14/93, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Law Inez Smith Reid Confirmation Resolution, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Law School Correspondence, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Education: Special Ed Prevocational School for the Handicapped 1 of 3, 1982-1991 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Education: Special Ed Prevocational School for the Handicapped 2 of 3, 1982-1991 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Education: Special Ed Prevocational School for the Handicapped 3 of 3, 1982-1991 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Education Recreational Center for the Handicapped, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - District of Columbia - 1980-1985 Capital Improvements Program, undated (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Review 1 of 2, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Review 2 of 2, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday May 9 1988 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Judiciary Committee Meeting Council Member June 16 1988 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Special Meeting 05/16/1988 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Friday July 1 1988 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Friday July 11 1988 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries March 28 1988 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Additional Meeting April 15 1988 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday April 25 1988 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday March 28 1988 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday Dec. 21 1987 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday March 14 1988 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - WMATA Coordinating Committee, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday Dec. 14 1987 1 of 2 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday Dec. 14 1987 1 of 2 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday Dec. 3 1990 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday Dec. 10 1990 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Charles Mason Room 122, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday February 8 1988 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Tues. March 1 1988 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday June 11 1990 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Proposal for Pay Raise for Educational Service Employees, 1986 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Comprehensive Resolution: Pay Adjustments/Compensation/Provisions/etc., 1988 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - A Citizen Guide: The District of Columbia's Fundamental Laws, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Sludge Hauling Plan Disturbs NW Neighbors, 1997 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Committee on Public Works and the Environment Public Hearing 5/4/94, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Committee on Public Works Budget Markup 28 May 96, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Committee on Public Works Committee Meeting/Markup 01 May 96, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Committee on Public Works Committee Meeting/Markup 03 Apr 96, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Clean up Articles and Correspondence, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Committee on Public Works and the Environment Public Meeting 1/4/95, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - Water Main System Annual Report Memos, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Public Works and the Environment Memos, 1995-1996 (Box 67, Folder 27)
  - Council of DC Committee on Public Works and the Environment Pubic Oversight Roundtable, 1996 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Wastewater Utility Revenue Requirements - Cost of Service and Rates, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - WSA Nominations 1 of 2, 1995-1996 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - WSA Nominations 2 of 2, 1995-1996 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Public Works and the Environment Pubic Hearing 03 May 95, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - District of Columbia Water and Sewer Authority, 1995-1996 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Woodrow Wilson Bridge, 1996 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Metropolitan Washington Regional Public Health and Drinking Water Conference, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Prioritization of Waste Transfer Services, 1993-1994 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Soil Processing Facility Bryant St. NE, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Solid Waste Facility Permit Act, 1995-1996 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - PA Ave, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - FY 97 Budget, 1996-1998 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - FY 96 Supp Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - FY 96 Budget, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - FY 95 Budget, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - FY 95 Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Recycling, 1995-1997 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Mulit Material Recycling Act, 1988-1996 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Alternative Fuels, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Tinted Window and Temp Tag Amendment Acts Hearing 1-19-94, 1990-1994 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Residential Parking Bills 11-335 8 11-348, 1996 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Resid Parking Subzone Act 11-348, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Pubic Parking Authority Bill 10 -532, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Impact of Parking Regs on Business, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Snow Plan, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Clunker Leg, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Public Works Sept. 19 1996 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Taxi Cab Commission 1 of 3, 1995-1996 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Taxi Cab Commission 2 of 3, 1994-1996 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Taxi Cab Commission 3 of 3, 1994-1996 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Diplomacy and Espionage, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 9)